export const data = [
    {
        question : "Which of the following is an instruction to the web browser about what version of the markup language the page is written in?",
        option1 : "Markup",
        option2 : "Meta tag",
        option3 : "DSS",
        option4 : "Doctype",
        ans : 4,
    },
    {
        question : "Which of the following is not an HTML tag?",
        option1 : "Doctype",
        option2 : "p",
        option3 : "Table",
        option4 : "Style",
        ans : 1,
    },
    {
        question : "How many ways can you apply colors in CSS?",
        option1 : "1",
        option2 : "3",
        option3 : "5",
        option4 : "7",
        ans : 4,
    },
    {
        question : "How can you clear a floated element?",
        option1 : "Clear:both",
        option2 : "Press the delete key",
        option3 : "Del tag",
        option4 : "Strike tag",
        ans : 1,
    },
    {
        question : "What are the two methods of forms transfer?",
        option1 : "Get and receive",
        option2 : "Get and post",
        option3 : "Post and recieve",
        option4 : "Post and take",
        ans : 2,
    },
    {
        question : "Which of the following is described as a collection of images put in a single image?",
        option1 : "Float",
        option2 : "Align",
        option3 : "Sprite",
        option4 : "Image",
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : "What should be the very last thing in an HTML document?",
        option1 : "Heading",
        option2 : "Title",
        option3 : "Body",
        option4 : "Doc type",
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : "A collection of data containing both properties and methods is called...",
        option1 : "Tag",
        option2 : "Selector",
        option3 : "Object",
        option4 : "Class",
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : "In JavaScript, 'this' refers to the object that ____ the object.",
        option1 : "Receives",
        option2 : "Depends",
        option3 : "Owns",
        option4 : "Direct",
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : "What is the runtime complexity of Fibonacci sequence?",
        option1 : "O(2^n)",
        option2 : "O(2n)",
        option3 : "(n)",
        option4 : "N(o)",
        ans : 1,
    },
]